Finding Aid for William Bolcom and Joan Morris Papers 1960-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound recordings
  - Audio-cassettes
    - Cole Porter 100th, Carnegie Hall, II, June 9, 1991 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Phoenix Symphony Orchestra, November 15, 1991 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Coming to America, I, AASO, January 18, 1992 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Coming to America, II, AASO, January 18, 1992 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Mohawk Trail Concerts, August 15, 1992 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Terrace, Kennedy Center, Washington DC, January 27, 1993 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Sedalia, MO, June 4-5, 1993 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Aspen Tent, 8 p.m., July 7, 1993 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - With Dick Hyman, Kerrytown, November 6, 1993 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Wigmore Hall, I, March 4, 1994 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Wigmore Hall, II, March 4, 1994 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Wigmore Hall, London, March 4, 1994 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Wall to Wall Berlin Interview, March 19, 1994 (Box 66, Item 3)
    - Mohawk Trail, Robert White/Joan Morris Part I, August 20, 1994; 2 audiocassettes (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Mohawk Trail, Robert White/Joan Morris Part II, August 20, 1994; 2 audiocassettes (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Mohawk Trail, Robert White/Joan Morris, August 20, 1994 (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Ann Arbor Symphony Orchestra, September 10, 1994; 4 audiocassettes (Box 66, Item 4)
    - The Cleveland Institute of Music, Darius Milhaud Society Presents, Madame Bovary, March 19, 1995; 2 audiocassettes (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Youmans, August 15, 1995 (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Chicago, Marriage and Love in the Songs of Irving Berlin, November 11, 1995; 2 audiocassettes (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Toledo, Peristyle, November 18, 1995 (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Cabaret, 92nd St. y, New York, January 20, 1996; 2 audiocassettes (Box 66, Item 4)
    - Cabaret Production, Side 1 & 2, February 25, 1996 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Cabaret Production, Side 3, February 25, 1996 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Dancing Bear Music Series, Red, White & Blue, Side A&B, May 18, 1996 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Dancing Bear Music Series, Red, White & Blue, Side C, May 18, 1996 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Bolcom & Morris, July 3, 1996 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - WHRO Benefit Concert, Norfolk, VA, October 27, 1996 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Mohawk, August 1997 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Mohawk 1997 Weinstein, August 1 & 2, 1997 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - 92nd St. Y, New York City, December 2, 1997 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - NMC Music Department Presents, May 2, 1998; 2 audiocassettes (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Ravinia Festival, Martin Theatre, June 15, 1998 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Tannery Pond Concerts, July 2001 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - U-C Berkeley, April 18, 2005; 2 audiocassettes (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Berlin Tribute, High Performance, undated; 3 audiocassettes (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Coca Cola, undated (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Don't Give the Name a Bad Place, undated (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Rodgers & Hart, CD, undated (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Session Takes, undated (Box 67, Item 2)
    - What'll I Do, etc., undated (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Youmans, II, undated; 2 audiocassettes (Box 67, Item 2)
  - DATs
    - An Evening with Bolcom and Morris, Aspen Music Festival, July 7, 1998 (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Just a Wearying for You, The Man Who Broke the Bank at Monte Carlo, November 26, 1993 (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Lime Jello Crowd, September 29, 2004 (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Youmans II, First Edition, undated (Box 67, Item 2)
  - Mini DVs
    - Berkeley Concerts, Winter/Spring 2005; 2 audiocassettes (Box 67, Item 2)
  - Compact discs
    - Roy Thompson Hall, Toronto, Canada (parts 1 and 2) (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Guelph Festival, recital, 1991 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Northeastern Illinois University Jewel Box Series, Let's Face the Music (parts 1 and 2), September 19, 2003; 2 optical disks CDs (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Sings Yip Harburg, with Morath, September 26, 2003 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Soundcheck, engineer, Irene Trudel, May 11, 2004 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Kerrytown, Ann Arbor, Afternoon, December 2007 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Kerrytown, Ann Arbor, Evening, December 2007 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Distinguished Artist Series, Waco, Texas, January 29, 2008; 2 optical disks CDs (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Swinging On A Star, Lancaster Festival, July 21, 2008 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Kerrytown Concert House, December 6, 2008 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Vocal Pieces, Concert, November 22, 2009 (Box 67, Item 3)